<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tantalus!</title>
    <link>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Tantalus!</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 16:31:37 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/about/</guid>
      
        <description>Songlin (Tantalus) is an undergraduate student in his senior year at Shanghai Jiao Tong University (SJTU). He has a general interest in developing understanding into computer systems, and assisting the authoring of better software.
Songlin is currently a research assistant at Lab of Cryptography and Computer Security, and he works primarily on software security. His paper &amp;ldquo;Accelerating SM2 Digital Signature Algorithm Using Modern Processor Features&amp;rdquo; has been accepted to ICICS&#39;19. Recently he is working on LLVM and Intel MPK for program hardening.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clang: Don&#39;t Touch My Code!</title>
      <link>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/post/clang-no-opt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 16:31:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/post/clang-no-opt/</guid>
      
        <description>Clang/LLVM is a toolchain that is widely adopted by both researchers and the industry. Based on LLVM, compilers for new targets are built, and program analysis solutions are developed, thanks to the well-defined LLVM IR. Nevertheless, Clang/LLVM is also famous for some of its strange (often just &amp;ldquo;different&amp;rdquo; from gcc) behaviors and very aggressive optimizations.
Recently I am working on LLVM (7.0) for program analysis and instrumentation, and I think it&#39;s time to write about how we are dealing with unwanted optimizations.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jan 2020 23:25:55 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://Tantalus13A98B5F.github.io/post/hello-world/</guid>
      
        <description>Hi, this is Tantalus. I&#39;m going to write about my life and my explorations. Cheers!</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
